<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
  <publisher>4 Corner Resources</publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://www.4cornerresources.com</publisherurl>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2026 09:35:43 EST</lastBuildDate>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Staff Accountant]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32433869]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/senior-staff-accountant-32433869/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Maitland]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[FL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Up to $75,000/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Maitland, FL · Hybrid<br><br>Employment Type: Direct Placement<br><br>Pay Rate: Up to $75,000/year<br><br>4 Corner Resources is seeking a Senior Staff Accountant to support a boutique law firm specializing in medical malpractice and healthcare-related litigation. This role combines accounting, reporting, and financial analysis while working closely with leadership to support day-to-day operations and business decision-making.<br><br>The ideal candidate is a senior-level accountant or bookkeeper who is highly organized, confident, and able to work independently. This person should be comfortable managing a high volume of transactions, keeping track of outstanding items, meeting deadlines, and taking ownership of routine accounting responsibilities with minimal supervision.<br><br>Senior Staff Accountant Responsibilities<br><br>- Assist with month-end close (cash basis), including closed case write-offs<br>- Receive, verify, and enter vendor invoices into accounting and case management systems<br>- Prepare and process weekly check runs<br>- Process client credit card transactions<br>- Manage payroll and PTO tracking through ADP Workforce Now<br>- Support case-related accounting, including settlement disbursements and trust-related processes<br>- Create closing statements for case settlements<br>- Prepare cost reports for mediations and lien negotiations<br>- Draft correspondence related to trust disbursements<br>- Maintain client files tied to case settlements<br>- Process annual 1099s and support tax package preparation for CPA<br>- Analyze financial data in QuickBooks Online and extract insights from case management systems (Filevine)<br>- Build reports to support operational and strategic decision-making<br>- Track and resolve outstanding accounting items<br>- Manage a high volume of transactions across operating accounts, cost accounts, and corporate credit cards<br>- Identify opportunities to improve processes and efficiency<br><br>Senior Staff Accountant Qualifications<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in Accounting, Finance, or related field required<br>- 7–10 years of accounting experience<br>- Proven experience with QuickBooks Online required<br>- Experience managing high transaction volumes and multiple priorities<br>- Ability to work independently with limited supervision<br>- Strong organizational, problem-solving, and follow-up skills<br>- Experience in a professional services environment preferred (law firm, CPA firm, or similar)<br>- Strong data analysis skills<br>- Advanced proficiency in Microsoft Excel and Office<br>- Excellent attention to detail and communication skills<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Experience with legal or trust accounting<br>- Familiarity with Filevine or similar case management systems<br>- Exposure to business intelligence or financial analysis<br>- Interest in automation, AI tools, or process improvement<br>- Experience with ADP Workforce Now<br><br>Additional Details<br><br>- Location: Maitland, FL<br>- Fully onsite Monday-Friday, with potential for 1 remote day per week after 90 days<br>- Compensation: $75,000 annually plus bonus eligibility twice per year<br>- Direct hire opportunity<br>- Benefits include health, dental, vision, 401(k) contribution, life insurance, long-term disability, paid holidays, and PTO<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Bilingual Customer Experience Evaluator]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32434175]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/bilingual-field-auditor-32434175/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Bronx]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[NY]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Up to $21/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Bronx, NY · Hybrid<br><br>Employment Type: Contract<br><br>Pay Rate: Up to $21/hour<br><br>Position Summary:<br>We are seeking two detail-oriented and discreet Bilingual Customer Experience Evaluators to evaluate the accuracy and compliance of enrollment activities. This role involves using approved scenarios and disguises to audit representatives in the field and over the phone, ensuring they align with current regulatory and internal standards. Your feedback will help drive improvements in service quality and compliance.<br><br>Requirements:<br><br>- High School Diploma required.<br>- 1 Candidate must be bilingual in English and Spanish.<br>- 1 Candidate must be English and Mandarin, Cantonese, or Fukienese.<br>- Strong proficiency in Microsoft Excel for reporting and documentation.<br>- Excellent attention to detail, verbal and written communication, and time management skills.<br>- Ability to create and wear disguises (e.g., wigs, hats, glasses) to ensure anonymity during audits.<br><br>Technical Skills:<br><br>- Comfortable using Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Outlook), iPhone apps, and web-based tools (e.g., Google Maps).<br>- Ability to accurately type, copy/paste, highlight, and format in Word and Excel.<br><br>Key Responsibilities:<br><br>- Conduct field and phone audits using scripted scenarios while maintaining an anonymous identity.<br>- Record and document encounters; transcribe interactions where applicable and flag any non-compliance or misinformation.<br>- Monitor sales representatives for adherence to company guidelines and federal/state regulations.<br>- Submit daily and weekly audit summaries using Excel-based templates.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32424351]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/it-business-analyst-32424351/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Orlando]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[FL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$50-$60/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>4 Corner Resources is seeking an IT Business Analyst for a fast-paced, project-driven enterprise IT environment. This role is ideal for a Business Analyst who thrives in Agile environments, enjoys collaborating across technical and business teams, and can drive projects from requirements gathering through deployment and support.<br><br>What you do:<br><br>- Gather and translate business requirements into user stories, use cases, and functional specs<br>- Serve as the liaison between business stakeholders and the IT delivery team<br>- Participate in daily Scrum ceremonies and manage backlog grooming and sprint planning<br>- Write and present change requests at the Change Advisory Board<br>- Coordinate release communications and implementation plans<br>- Support UAT, hypercare, and root cause analysis post go-live<br>- Step into a Product Owner role when there is no dedicated PO on the project<br><br>What you bring:<br><br>- Proven BA experience in an IT environment<br>- Strong knowledge of Agile and Scrum methodology<br>- Hands-on experience with Jira, ADO, or similar tools<br>- Experience with CAB processes and ITSM frameworks<br>- Ability to write detailed functional documentation<br>- Strong stakeholder management and facilitation skills<br><br>Additional Details:<br><br>- Location: Orlando, FL<br>- Length: 6-12 month contract (potential for conversion)<br>- Schedule: Monday-Friday 8:00AM-5:00PM<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Field Service Manager]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32424824]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/field-service-manager-32424824/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: On-site in York, Pennsylvania<br><br>Pay Rate: $90,000 – $171,000 per year depending on experience. Seniority will significantly affect compensation for this role.<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time, Direct Hire<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking a Manager of Field Services, Site Management to lead the planning and execution of field site activities for hydroelectric projects. This position is responsible for ensuring projects are completed safely, on schedule, within budget, and according to established quality requirements.<br><br>The Manager will oversee site management personnel, establish field execution procedures, support project staffing, monitor field performance, and provide leadership to Site Managers and Supervisors.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Oversee the execution of field service activities across assigned projects.<br>- Develop and maintain standard processes, procedures, and tools for planning and executing field site activities.<br>- Ensure field operations comply with technical requirements and applicable legal and regional regulations.<br>- Identify, hire, assign, coach, and manage Site Managers and Supervisors.<br>- Ensure project sites are properly staffed according to project execution plans.<br>- Oversee timekeeping and compensation processes for field labor and supervisory personnel.<br>- Establish qualification requirements and coordinate necessary training initiatives.<br>- Monitor and improve safety, quality, and overall performance at project sites.<br>- Support field activity planning and the implementation of standardized planning systems and tools.<br>- Ensure work procedures and quality plans are available and followed.<br>- Monitor project costs, identify potential risks, and implement corrective actions.<br>- Promote best practices and lessons learned across field sites.<br>- Support the implementation of site layouts, infrastructure, tooling, and fixtures.<br>- Oversee site purchasing and sourcing activities.<br><br>Requirements<br><br>- High school diploma or GED.<br>- Previous experience in a supervisory or management position.<br>- Previous experience as a Site Manager or Supervisor on hydro turbine or generator projects.<br>- Ability to read and interpret blueprints, specifications, project schedules, and budgets.<br>- Strong communication, leadership, and interpersonal skills.<br>- Proficiency with Microsoft Office.<br>- Ability to travel occasionally to field sites.<br>- Ability to work in both office and active field site environments.<br>- Ability to stand and walk for extended periods and occasionally lift, reach, stoop, or crouch.<br>- Ability to work safely in field environments that may have elevated noise levels.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Project Engineer]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32421295]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/project-engineer-32421295/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Neenah]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[WI]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: On-site in Neenah, Wisconsin<br><br>Pay Rate: $70,000 – $100,000 / year<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time, Direct Hire<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking an Engineer II, Projects to manage customer projects within a roll shop environment. This position will provide engineering, technical, commercial, and project management support from the initial quotation through project completion.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Manage customer projects from initial quotation through completion.<br>- Communicate with customers regarding engineering designs, project requirements, pricing, questions, and project progress.<br>- Prepare project quotations, supporting documentation, preliminary design proposals, and scopes of work for mechanical services, modifications, repairs, and testing.<br>- Review customer drawings, specifications, and related documentation to determine project requirements and component feasibility.<br>- Serve as a liaison between engineering and mechanical service operations.<br>- Work with mechanical personnel to resolve manufacturing and design issues.<br>- Coordinate with purchasing, quality control, sales, production, accounting, metal finishing, assembly, vendors, and outside sales representatives.<br>- Generate and update process documentation, work instructions, flowcharts, and related engineering documents.<br>- Participate in engineering and general design reviews.<br>- Identify and support cost-reduction and process-improvement opportunities.<br>- Assist with root-cause investigations and corrective actions.<br>- Generate and track KPI data and corrective action progress.<br>- Support safety investigations, safety initiatives, Lean practices, and Operational Excellence programs.<br>- Manage multiple projects and priorities while meeting customer and business deadlines.<br><br>Requirements<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in engineering from an accredited four-year college or university. Relevant professional experience may be considered in place of a college degree.<br>- Proficiency with Microsoft Office applications, ERP systems, and electronic document control systems.<br>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.<br>- Ability to communicate effectively with engineers, customers, vendors, and shop-floor team members.<br>- Strong project management, troubleshooting, analytical, and problem-solving skills.<br>- Ability to independently manage multiple projects, responsibilities, and deadlines.<br>- Ability to prioritize responsibilities and make sound decisions in a deadline-driven environment.<br>- Professional, personable, and diplomatic communication style.<br>- Self-motivated and capable of working independently with limited supervision.<br>- Ability to teach, coach, and support other team members.<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Experience working within a manufacturing environment.<br>- Previous project management experience.<br>- Knowledge of paper machine rolls, paper manufacturing equipment, or paper mill operations.<br>- Experience reviewing engineering drawings, specifications, and manufacturing requirements.<br>- Experience supporting mechanical repair, modification, or testing projects.<br>- Familiarity with Lean manufacturing and Operational Excellence principles.<br><br>Physical Requirements<br><br>- Ability to stand for extended periods, walk, and reach with hands and arms.<br>- Ability to lift and move up to 50 pounds.<br>- Ability to perform work requiring close vision, distance vision, color vision, depth perception, and the ability to adjust focus.<br>- Ability to work within indoor office and manufacturing shop environments.<br>- May be exposed to noise, welding activities, grinding dust, and fumes within shop areas.<br>- Ability to travel up to 10% as business needs require.<br><br>This job description is intended to provide a general overview of the position and is not an all-inclusive list of responsibilities, requirements, or working conditions.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineer II]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32415446]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/mechanical-engineer-ii-32415446/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: On-site in York, Pennsylvania<br><br>Pay Rate: Up to $110,000 / year<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time, Direct Hire<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking an Engineer 2 to develop engineering design solutions from project inception through production. This position will work with reduced supervision and guidance from experienced engineering professionals to solve routine design problems, support customer projects, and contribute to process improvement and standardization initiatives.<br><br>The Engineer 2 may serve as the lead engineer for smaller projects and perform component engineering for rehabilitation projects and new components. This role will support projects from the proposal stage through manufacturing, installation, testing, and project completion.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Prepare and update engineering designs for customer projects.<br>- Provide technical project leadership from contract award through project completion.<br>- Support proposals by preparing preliminary engineering designs and technical solutions.<br>- Define sourcing and manufacturing strategies beginning during the proposal stage.<br>- Create 3D solid models of components and assemblies.<br>- Prepare 2D manufacturing drawings independently or in collaboration with designers.<br>- Operate CAD and CAE software to complete engineering assignments.<br>- Perform required design calculations using standard engineering principles, hand calculations, and proprietary design tools.<br>- Review and release engineering documents and bills of materials in consultation with experienced engineers.<br>- Locate and evaluate OEM drawings from internal archives and customer-provided drawing files.<br>- Use SAP to create bills of materials that support manufacturing, sourcing, logistics, and installation requirements.<br>- Participate in and lead engineering design reviews.<br>- Prepare design revisions and process engineering change notifications.<br>- Provide dispositions for nonconforming materials, manufactured components, assemblies, and installed or tested equipment.<br>- Assist with the development of engineering schedules for assigned projects.<br>- Communicate project progress, milestones, workload, challenges, and potential delays to supervisors.<br>- Collaborate with manufacturing, sourcing, logistics, vendors, and field service teams to develop cost-effective design and installation solutions.<br>- Support quality teams with continuous improvement and problem-solving initiatives.<br>- Assist test engineers during equipment startup and commissioning.<br>- Evaluate test results and verify equipment performance against guaranteed values.<br>- Prepare technical reports, forms, and project documentation.<br>- Communicate with customers regarding engineering design questions and concerns.<br>- Contribute to engineering process improvement and standardization initiatives.<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in Engineering.<br>- Three to five years of engineering experience with a demonstrated record of successful project execution.<br>- Custom engineering design experience involving wind turbines, turbine generators, gas turbines, or related equipment within the energy sector.<br>- Experience developing engineering designs, calculations, drawings, and technical documentation.<br>- Ability to create or review 3D models, 2D drawings, and bills of materials.<br>- Strong teamwork and collaboration skills.<br>- Excellent written and verbal communication skills.<br>- Ability to manage multiple priorities based on changing business needs.<br>- Strong organizational and time-management skills.<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Experience supporting industrial equipment, rehabilitation projects, or engineered-to-order products.<br>- Experience using CAD or CAE design software.<br>- Experience creating bills of materials in SAP.<br>- Experience supporting manufacturing, sourcing, installation, testing, or commissioning activities.<br>- Experience providing technical leadership for smaller engineering projects.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Outpatient Quality Improvement Consultant]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32401403]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/outpatient-quality-improvement-consultant-32401403/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Fully remote]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$70,000-$85,000/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Remote in Florida<br><br>Salary / Pay Range: $78,000 – $85,000 annually<br><br>Employment Type: Direct Placement<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking an Outpatient Quality Improvement Consultant to support physician practices, outpatient clinics, and ambulatory healthcare organizations in improving patient outcomes, preventive care performance, and operational efficiency across multiple states.<br><br>This role partners with providers, practice leadership, and interdisciplinary teams to evaluate workflows, analyze quality metrics, identify care gaps, and support performance improvement initiatives in outpatient healthcare settings. The organization offers a collaborative, remote-first culture focused on advancing quality care delivery and population health outcomes.<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in nursing, public health, healthcare administration, or related field<br>- 3+ years of experience in outpatient healthcare, physician practice operations, population health, managed care, or ambulatory quality improvement<br>- Experience with HEDIS, preventive care metrics, chronic disease management, or value-based care initiatives<br>- Familiarity with quality improvement methodologies such as root cause analysis, PDSA, and process mapping<br>- Experience interpreting EHR data, quality dashboards, and provider performance metrics<br>- Strong communication and provider relationship management skills<br>- Ability to work independently in a remote environment and manage multiple priorities<br><br>Preferred Backgrounds<br><br>- Population Health Specialist<br>- HEDIS or Quality Improvement Coordinator<br>- Clinical Operations Manager<br>- Practice Administrator<br>- Managed Care Quality Specialist<br>- Care Management or Value-Based Care Professional<br>- Outpatient Quality Analyst<br><br>Day-to-Day Responsibilities<br><br>- Support outpatient providers with quality improvement and workflow optimization initiatives<br>- Analyze preventive care metrics, chronic disease outcomes, and quality performance data<br>- Identify care gaps and guide providers on documentation and operational best practices<br>- Assist practices with performance improvement initiatives tied to CMS and value-based care measures<br>- Monitor provider progress and maintain quality-related documentation within assigned systems<br>- Build relationships with physician practices and outpatient clinical teams across assigned territories<br><br>Benefits<br><br>- Comprehensive medical, dental, and vision coverage<br>- 401(k) with employer contribution<br>- Generous PTO and paid holidays<br>- Remote-first work environment<br>- Friday schedules ending at noon<br>- All travel expenses covered for required meetings<br><br>Culture<br><br>This organization is known for its collaborative and mission-driven environment. Leadership is stable, employee retention is high, and many team members describe the culture as supportive, flexible, and aligned with a shared commitment to improving healthcare. Growth paths exist within a matrix structure, allowing advancement from Associate to Consultant to Senior Consultant levels.<br><br>Salary / Pay Range<br><br>$78,000 – $85,000 annually<br><br>Work Schedule<br><br>Monday–Friday, 8:30 AM – 5:00 PM<br><br>Remote in Florida<br><br>Minimal travel outside of the two required annual meetings<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Nursing Home Quality Improvement Consultant]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32401286]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/nursing-home-quality-improvement-consultant-32401286/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Fully remote]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$70,000-$85,000/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Remote<br><br>Salary / Pay Range: $78,000 – $85,000 annually<br><br>Employment Type: Direct Placement<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking a Nursing Home Quality Improvement Consultant to support Skilled Nursing Facilities and Long Term Care providers in improving patient outcomes, strengthening regulatory performance, and enhancing quality measures across multiple states.<br><br>This role partners directly with Nursing Home Administrators, Directors of Nursing, MDS leaders, and interdisciplinary teams to analyze quality data, identify operational gaps, support QAPI initiatives, and guide performance improvement efforts. The organization offers a highly collaborative, remote-first environment focused on improving care delivery within post acute and long term care settings.<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in nursing, public health, healthcare administration, or related field<br>- 3+ years of experience within Skilled Nursing Facilities or nursing home<br>- Must have experience working as a Licensed Nursing Home Administrator (LNHA) or Director of Nursing (DON)<br>- Experience with QAPI, CMS quality measures, Five-Star Ratings, survey readiness, or regulatory compliance<br>- Familiarity with root cause analysis, process mapping, PDSA, and quality improvement methodologies<br>- Experience interpreting MDS, EHR, or quality performance data<br>- Strong communication and relationship-building skills with nursing home leadership teams<br>- Ability to work independently in a remote environment and manage multiple priorities<br><br>Preferred Backgrounds<br><br>- Director of Nursing (DON)<br>- Assistant Director of Nursing (ADON)<br>- Nursing Home Administrator (NHA/LNHA)<br><br>Day-to-Day Responsibilities<br><br>- Support nursing homes with quality improvement initiatives and regulatory performance<br>- Analyze quality metrics related to falls, infections, rehospitalizations, weight loss, antipsychotic use, and CMS measures<br>- Guide facilities through QAPI initiatives and process improvement strategies<br>- Assist providers with survey readiness, Plans of Correction, and operational improvement efforts<br>- Interpret MDS and EHR data to identify trends and opportunities for improvement<br>- Maintain ongoing communication with facility leadership teams and assigned provider groups<br><br>Benefits<br><br>- Comprehensive medical, dental, and vision coverage<br>- 401(k) with employer contribution<br>- Generous PTO and paid holidays<br>- Remote-first work environment<br>- Friday schedules ending at noon<br>- All travel expenses covered for required meetings<br><br>Culture<br><br>This organization is known for its collaborative and mission-driven environment. Leadership is stable, employee retention is high, and many team members describe the culture as supportive, flexible, and aligned with a shared commitment to improving healthcare. Growth paths exist within a matrix structure, allowing advancement from Associate to Consultant to Senior Consultant levels.<br><br>Salary / Pay Range<br><br>$78,000 – $85,000 annually<br><br>Work Schedule<br><br>Monday–Friday, 8:30 AM – 5:00 PM<br><br>Remote role requiring residency within designated states: Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Louisiana, Mississippi, North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee, Virginia, Arkansas, and West Virginia<br><br>Minimal travel outside of the two required annual meetings<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Field Service Spares Engineer]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32374806]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/field-service-spares-engineer-32374806/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Appleton]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[WI]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: On-site in Appleton, Wisconsin<br><br>Pay Rate: $82,000 – $100,000<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time, Direct Hire<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking a Technical Spare Parts Specialist to support technical spare parts identification, design, documentation, and customer support. This role will work closely with engineering, manufacturing, sales, purchasing, quality, service teams, and customers to ensure accurate part identification, technical recommendations, and support for parts and services needs.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Identify parts from assemblies, multi-drawings, and technical documentation<br>- Create, adapt, and revise 2D/3D models and drawings<br>- Define tolerances and specifications in alignment with standards under guidance<br>- Support the creation of Material Masters for identified parts<br>- Prepare maintenance kits, BOMs, and technical recommendations<br>- Support cost department and sales teams with technical arguments and documentation<br>- Conduct customer site visits for equipment inspections and technical recommendations<br>- Assist customers with detailed explanations of requested parts<br>- Communicate directly with customers regarding spare parts requests<br>- Apply knowledge of part life cycle and equipment processes<br>- Determine the best source for purchased and manufactured parts using local and international suppliers<br>- Support warranty investigations, vendors, and workshop teams with inputs and documentation<br>- Participate in continuous improvement of processes, standards, and customer satisfaction<br>- Travel up to 20% for customer visits and production floor work<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in Mechanical Engineering, Industrial Engineering, or a related engineering field, or proven technical experience in spare parts or a related industry<br>- Previous knowledge of paper machines or paper production processes<br>- Experience with technical drawing interpretation<br>- Experience with CAD software<br>- Strong analytical and problem-solving skills<br>- Hands-on experience in technical environments<br>- Ability to work independently and collaborate cross-functionally<br>- Strong communication skills with technical and non-technical audiences<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Previous experience in parts and services<br>- Paper industry experience<br>- Experience with SAP<br>- Experience with documentation systems<br><br>Company Benefits &amp; Culture<br><br>This is a full-time, direct hire opportunity with the client. This role offers the opportunity to work in a highly visible technical position supporting spare parts, service, engineering, manufacturing, sales, purchasing, quality, and customer-facing initiatives. The position is well-suited for someone who enjoys applying technical expertise, working cross-functionally, and supporting a growing segment of the organization.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Training Specialist]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32368378]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/franchise-corporate-trainer-32368378/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Ocala]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[FL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$60,000–$63,000/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Ocala, FL · Onsite<br><br>Salary: $60,000–$63,000/year<br><br>Employment Type: Full-time, direct hire<br><br>4 Corner Resources is seeking a Training Specialist on behalf of our client, a rapidly expanding franchise organization. This role is instrumental in helping franchise owners succeed through operational training, ongoing consulting, and consistent oversight that protects and strengthens the brand.<br><br>Willingness to travel across Florida and out of state approximately 85% of the time is required.<br><br>Training Specialist Key Responsibilities<br><br>- Deliver structured training programs before, during, and after store openings, ensuring franchisees are fully equipped to operate independently.<br>- Serve as a trusted advisor to franchise owners, building strong, collaborative relationships through clear communication and hands-on support.<br>- Conduct regular on-site visits to evaluate performance, provide coaching, and identify opportunities for operational improvement.<br>- Monitor franchisee compliance with company policies, operational procedures, and brand standards to maintain consistency across all locations.<br>- Provide tailored consulting and problem-solving support to help franchise owners overcome challenges, improve profitability, and drive long-term business growth.<br>- Gather feedback from franchisees and share insights with leadership to inform future training and operational strategies.<br>- Maintain accurate training records, reports, and evaluations to track franchisee progress and overall program effectiveness.<br><br>Training Specialist Qualifications<br><br>- Proven background in operational leadership, with Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) management experience strongly preferred.<br>- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with a personable and approachable style and patience in building relationships.<br>- Strong business acumen, with a consultative approach to problem solving and guiding franchisees toward improved results.<br>- Highly motivated, proactive, and able to balance independent work with supporting multiple stakeholders.<br>- Demonstrated ability to manage travel, schedules, and priorities while maintaining focus on long-term goals.<br>- Willingness and ability to travel 85% of the time to support franchise operations across Florida and select out-of-state markets.<br><br>Training Specialist Additional Details<br><br>- Full-time, direct hire position<br>- Flexible schedule required, including willingness to work weekends for store openings<br>- Primary territory covers Jacksonville, Ocala, and Lake City, FL with out-of-state travel as needed<br>- Salary starting at $60k annually, with flexibility based on experience<br>- Competitive compensation package including:<br>  - Health, dental, and vision insurance<br>  - 401(k) with company match<br>  - Paid time off and paid holidays<br>  - Company vehicle provided or mileage reimbursement if using personal vehicle<br>  - Covered travel expenses<br>  - Supportive, growth-focused work environment<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Site Supervisor]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32324805]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/site-supervisor-32324805/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Job Title: Site Supervisor<br><br>Location: Can be located anywhere in the U.S – 95% travel required<br><br>Salary / Pay Range: $100,000 annually plus bonus<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time<br><br>Our client is seeking a Site Supervisor to plan, prepare, and supervise the disassembly and installation of hydro power plant equipment at field sites. This role will oversee work involving hydro-turbines, generators, control equipment, and related support equipment while directing craft labor crews and subcontractors to ensure work is completed safely, accurately, on schedule, and within budget.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Direct foremen, craft labor, and subcontractors for assigned work scopes<br>- Supervise disassembly, maintenance, rehabilitation, and installation activities for hydro turbines, generators, and auxiliary systems<br>- Support safety planning and enforce site safety rules and procedures<br>- Perform detailed planning and preparation for assigned work scopes, including handoffs with support groups<br>- Work with engineering, quality, and customer teams to clarify technical procedures, drawings, and field data requirements<br>- Identify and mitigate safety and quality risks during planning and execution<br>- Ensure materials and components meet specifications and are free of defects before installation<br>- Plan and ensure availability of fixtures, tools, and required equipment<br>- Ensure quality requirements are understood, measured, inspected, and documented as required<br>- Escalate safety, technical, quality, or schedule issues to the Site Manager<br>- Support workforce capacity planning with the Site Manager<br>- Promote a professional and supportive work environment with craft labor and subcontractors<br>- Identify and document schedule and quality deviations<br>- Lead site incident investigations for safety and quality issues and drive corrective actions<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- High school diploma required<br>- Minimum of 5 years of experience<br>- Minimum of 3 years of relevant experience in construction, hydro preferred, or journeyman trades in a leadership role<br>- Ability to identify and mitigate safety risks while maintaining a safe work environment for all site personnel<br>- Strong attention to detail and accuracy<br>- Excellent organizational and communication skills<br>- Excellent spoken and written English skills<br>- Ability to engage vendors and engineering personnel to define solutions that reduce cost and risk<br>- Ability to provide leadership and ensure compliant execution according to contractual requirements<br>- Ability to support project objectives related to safety, quality, schedule, and cost<br>- OSHA 30 certification<br>- Ability to meet physical requirements of the role, including use of PPE, lifting up to 50 lbs., climbing ladders and stairs, working in confined spaces, and working at heights<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Hydro construction experience<br>- General Foreman or similar field leadership experience<br>- Experience supervising installation, maintenance, or rehabilitation work involving turbines, generators, or auxiliary systems<br><br>Company Benefits &amp; Culture<br><br>Our client offers the opportunity to support technical field service work in a hands-on hydro power environment. This role works closely with site management, craft labor, subcontractors, engineering, quality, and customer teams to support safe, efficient, and contract-compliant project execution.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Site Manager]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32324768]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/site-manager-32324768/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Job Title: Site Manager<br><br>Location: Can be located anywhere in the U.S – 95% travel required<br><br>Salary / Pay Range: $100,000 annually plus bonus<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time<br><br>Our client is seeking a Site Manager to oversee site supervision and site project management for hydro power plant equipment installations, upgrades, and maintenance. This role will support hydro-turbine, generator, control equipment, and related electrical and mechanical systems while ensuring work is completed safely, on schedule, within budget, and in accordance with contractual and quality requirements.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Serve as the single point of accountability for site work planning, performance, and site employees<br>- Perform detailed planning for site work, including interfaces and handoffs with support groups<br>- Lead erection and commissioning efforts for hydro-electric equipment and supporting systems<br>- Manage site performance related to safety, quality, cost, schedule, and scope<br>- Maintain strong customer relationships through clear communication and professional site standards<br>- Oversee financial performance of on-site activities<br>- Identify and communicate additional sales opportunities with sales and project management<br>- Support continuous improvement by sharing best practices and lessons learned<br>- Work closely with project management to ensure contractual obligations are met<br>- Support safety planning and enforce site safety rules and procedures<br>- Identify and mitigate safety and quality risks during planning and execution<br>- Lead site teams, craft labor, and subcontractors in a professional and supportive manner<br>- Document schedule, quality, and scope deviations<br>- Lead incident investigations for safety and quality issues and drive corrective actions<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- High school diploma required<br>- Bachelor of Engineering or equivalent relevant experience<br>- Minimum of 10 years of professional experience<br>- Minimum of 5 years of relevant experience in construction, hydro preferred, or journeyman trades in leadership roles<br>- Technical understanding of hydroelectric power plant equipment, rotating machinery, heavy manufacturing, or heavy construction<br>- Ability to manage 1 or 2 systems such as generator, turbine, E-BoP, M-BoP, steel structures, or hydraulics<br>- Ability to manage one area of a construction or rehabilitation project, such as powerhouse, intake, substation, dam, onsite manufacturing, or tunnel<br>- Ability to identify and mitigate safety risks while maintaining a safe work environment<br>- Understanding of contractual terms and conditions related to commercial project execution<br>- Experience identifying change work or claim opportunities and supporting documentation efforts<br>- Experience leading craft labor and professional teams<br>- Strong attention to detail and accuracy<br>- Excellent organizational and communication skills<br>- Strong spoken and written English skills<br>- Ability to engage vendors and engineering teams to define solutions that reduce cost and risk<br>- Ability to meet physical requirements of the role, including use of PPE, lifting up to 50 lbs., climbing ladders and stairs, working in confined spaces, and working at heights<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Hydro construction or hydro rehabilitation project experience<br>- General Foreman or similar site leadership experience<br>- Experience managing field work involving generator, turbine, electrical balance of plant, mechanical balance of plant, steel structures, or hydraulics<br><br>Company Benefits &amp; Culture<br><br>Our client offers the opportunity to lead field site operations on technical hydro power projects. This role works closely with project management, field service leadership, customers, subcontractors, suppliers, craft labor, and engineering teams to support safe, efficient, and contract-compliant project execution.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Field Service Engineer]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32324704]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/field-service-engineer-32324704/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Job Title: Field Service Engineer<br><br>Location: York, PA<br><br>Salary / Pay Range: $90,000 annually<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time<br><br>Our client is seeking a Field Service Engineer to plan and manage the field service scope of projects while ensuring work is completed within budget, schedule, quality, and safety requirements. This role will support proposals, project execution, site planning, technical reviews, and field service coordination for turbine, generator, and balance of plant equipment projects.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Develop field service concepts, execution plans, and cost estimates for project proposals<br>- Review technical requirements, customer specifications, and applicable legal or regional regulations<br>- Participate in site assessments and ensure required project information is available<br>- Support customer clarifications and field service planning during proposal and execution phases<br>- Prepare specifications for purchased services and supplies and evaluate bids or offers<br>- Identify risks and opportunities during the proposal phase and define contingency plans<br>- Support project startup and detail field service plans during execution<br>- Participate in design review meetings and provide field-related input<br>- Develop project-specific procedures, safety assessments, HSE documents, and quality plans<br>- Determine site layouts, tooling, fixtures, and infrastructure requirements<br>- Support project managers and site managers in executing field service scope<br>- Monitor quality, schedule, and cost targets and support corrective actions as needed<br>- Coordinate internal and external resources required for field service work<br>- Provide technical support and guidance to field sites<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- University diploma in Engineering or equivalent industry experience<br>- Technical understanding of turbines, generators, and balance of plant equipment<br>- Ability to read and interpret blueprints, specifications, schedules, and budgets<br>- Project management experience<br>- Strong communication and interpersonal skills<br>- Proficiency with Microsoft Office Suite<br>- Ability to travel to various project sites as needed<br>- Ability to meet physical requirements of the role, including use of PPE, lifting up to 50 lbs., climbing ladders and stairs, working in confined spaces, and working at heights<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Previous experience as a site manager or supervisor on hydro turbine or generator projects<br>- Field service experience within industrial, power generation, hydro, or heavy equipment environments<br>- Experience supporting project proposals, site planning, and field execution activities<br><br>Company Benefits &amp; Culture<br><br>Our client offers the opportunity to support technical field service projects in a hands-on, project-based environment. This role works closely with project teams, customers, suppliers, engineering, quality, purchasing, logistics, and field service leadership to ensure successful project execution from proposal through completion.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Operations Manager]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32454225]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/operations-manager-32454225/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Springfield]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[OR]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Springfield, OR<br><br>Employment Type: Direct Hire | Full-Time<br><br>Pay Rate: $150,000 – $200,000 / year<br><br>Introduction<br><br>The client is seeking an experienced Manager of Operations to lead all aspects of their Springfield, OR production facility. This site employs approximately 40 team members who support the paper industry through mechanical services and the production of covers for paper machine rolls. The Manager of Operations will be accountable for achieving annual targets across safety, quality, efficiency, production, and profitability, while developing and executing a clear operational strategy.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Provide clear direction aligned with site strategy, goals, and commitments, with a strong emphasis on safety, quality, and financial performance<br>- Foster a high-performance, collaborative, and inclusive work environment<br>- Drive employee engagement through transparent communication on business objectives and performance<br>- Maintain and execute succession plans, including development actions for high-potential employees and corrective actions for performance gaps<br>- Initiate documented solutions to address gaps in safety, quality, or financial performance<br>- Ensure consistent achievement of safety, quality, production, and efficiency targets<br>- Identify and optimize critical aspects of the operation through data-driven decision-making<br>- Embed standardized systems and continuous improvement practices (Lean, OE) across the operation<br>- Partner with Sales and Product Management to understand and meet customer expectations for delivery and quality<br>- Lead improvement and capital projects at the site<br>- Communicate regularly with employees and leadership regarding business results, performance levels, and operational priorities<br>- Promote clarity of expectations, alignment to goals, and accountability for results<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Minimum of 5 years of leadership experience, including at least 1 year in operations management<br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in a technical or business discipline, or equivalent experience<br>- Knowledge and experience with operational excellence, lean manufacturing, and continuous improvement practices<br>- Proficiency with MRP/ERP systems and data analytics tools (JD Edwards, Power BI, Pyramid BI)<br>- Ability to extract, analyze, and interpret data to support decision-making<br>- Proven ability to coach, mentor, and develop employees at all levels<br>- Strong communication skills and customer-service orientation<br>- Must be able to work full-time onsite at the Springfield, OR facility<br>- Ability to meet physical demands of an industrial environment, including standing, walking, and occasional travel<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Familiarity with AI and low-code technologies such as MS Copilot, Power Apps, or MS Forms<br>- Experience leading capital improvement projects<br>- Background in the paper, industrial, or manufacturing sector<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32491485]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/service-desk-analyst-32491485/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Orlando]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[FL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$15-$20/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>4 Corner Resources is hiring multiple Service Desk Analysts for one of Central Florida&#x27;s largest and most respected healthcare organizations. These are 6-month contract opportunities with the potential for extension or permanent hire. This is an excellent opportunity for IT professionals looking to gain experience in an enterprise healthcare environment while building their technical support skills.<br><br>Service Desk Analyst Responsibilities:<br><br>- Serve as the first point of contact for end users seeking technical assistance<br>- Provide phone-based support by troubleshooting issues, answering questions, researching solutions, and documenting resolutions<br>- Support users with issues related to the organization&#x27;s Electronic Medical Record (EMR) system<br>- Create, update, and manage support tickets while maintaining accurate documentation<br>- Escalate complex issues to the appropriate support teams when necessary<br>- Deliver exceptional customer service while meeting service-level expectations<br><br>Service Desk Analyst Qualifications:<br><br>- At least 1 year of technical support, help desk, or service desk experience<br>- Experience working with ticketing systems such as ServiceNow, Salesforce Service Cloud, Remedy, or similar platforms<br>- Minimum of 3 years of customer service experience<br>- Proficiency with Microsoft Office applications<br>- Strong communication, troubleshooting, and problem-solving skills<br>- Ability to work independently in a hybrid work environment<br><br>Service Desk Analyst Details:<br><br>- Location: Orlando, FL<br>- Schedule: Hybrid (1 day onsite, 4 days remote)<br>- Training: Fully onsite in Orlando, FL (1-4 weeks)<br>- Availability: Must have open availability, including nights, weekends, and rotating shifts<br>- Pay Rate: Up to $19.00/hour<br>- Duration: 6-month contract (with potential for extension or permanent placement based on performance and budget)<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Controls Design Engineer]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32491769]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/automation-designer-32491769/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Appleton]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[WI]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Starting at $75,000/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Appleton, WI<br>Employment Type: Direct Hire<br>Pay Rate: Up to $75,000<br><br>This is an entry/junior level role on an automation engineering team responsible for the design, upgrade, and integration of controls systems on active paper production equipment. It&#x27;s suited for someone with 0 to 5 years of experience in industrial controls looking to build a career in a technically engaging, drawing-intensive environment.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Create and update electrical schematics, wiring diagrams, biopanel layouts, junction box panel drawings, and interface/network drawings using CAD software<br>- Enter parts, materials, and documentation into SAP (ERP system)<br>- Coordinate with vendors and visit vendor facilities to support equipment builds and inspect completed assemblies<br>- Manage spare parts inventory and materials sourcing<br>- Support machine upgrades and enhancements on existing field equipment<br>- Review designs for compliance with engineering standards and customer specifications<br>- Collaborate with internal teams including sales, supply chain, manufacturing, and quality to maintain project schedules<br>- Assist in developing design standards and supporting senior automation engineers<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Background in industrial controls<br>- Experience with Rockwell Automation components<br>- Proficiency with CAD software for electrical/controls design (AutoCAD E or COMOS preferred)<br>- Ability to commute to or relocate to Appleton, WI<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Associates degree or higher in Electromechanical Design or a related field<br>- Experience with SAP or similar ERP systems<br>- Paper or pulp mill industry background<br>- Familiarity with pneumatic and/or hydraulic systems<br><br>Compensation and Benefits<br><br>- Up to $75,000 based on experience<br>- Hybrid schedule available (Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday in-office minimum per corporate policy)<br>- Minimal travel required; most vendors are local to the Appleton area<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Strategic Account Manager]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32489126]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/strategic-account-manager-32489126/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[LA]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Remote | Alabama, Louisiana, Oklahoma, and Mississippi (up to 60% travel)<br>Pay Rate: $143,000 / salary<br>Employment Type: Full-Time | Exempt<br><br>Introduction<br>The client is looking for a results-driven Strategic Account Manager to own and grow a portfolio of key accounts in the Pulp and Paper industry. You&#x27;ll serve as the primary point of contact for Products &amp; Services, acting as a trusted advisor while identifying new business opportunities and delivering solutions that drive growth on both sides of the relationship.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Own account plans and deliver on KPIs including orders, sales, profitability, win rate, and NPS<br>- Serve as the primary client contact for Products &amp; Services across your account portfolio<br>- Lead contract negotiations, pricing discussions, and service agreements<br>- Collaborate with internal technical and product teams to develop tailored client solutions<br>- Build and strengthen relationships from the C-suite to the plant floor<br>- Stay current on market trends, competitive offerings, and customer developments to differentiate the client&#x27;s value<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in Business, Engineering, Chemistry, or related field<br>- 5+ years of account management or sales experience<br>- Strong understanding of Pulp and Paper manufacturing processes and market dynamics<br>- Exceptional communication, negotiation, and presentation skills<br>- Willingness to travel up to 60% across Alabama, Louisiana, Oklahoma, and Mississippi<br>- Proficiency with Microsoft Office Suite<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Experience leading cross-functional or multi-disciplinary teams<br>- Background in value-based selling and strategic account planning<br>- Familiarity with industrial or manufacturing customer environments<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Inbound Customer Service Representative]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32480501]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/inbound-customer-service-representative-32480501/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[SC]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract to Hire]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$17-$19/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Myrtle Beach, SC · Onsite<br><br>Employment Type: Contract to Hire<br><br>Pay Rate: $17–$19/hour<br><br>We&#x27;re looking for upbeat, motivated individuals to join our Inbound Customer Service team, helping guests make the most of their vacation packages. You&#x27;ll guide callers through planning and booking their trips, offering expert advice, resolving concerns, and creating a positive, memorable experience from start to finish. If you&#x27;re energized by great conversations and enjoy making someone&#x27;s day, this could be the perfect fit.<br><br>Inbound Customer Service Representative Available Shifts and Pay<br><br>- AM Shift | Monday – Friday | 9:00 AM – 4:00 PM | $17/hour + bonuses<br>- PM Shift | Monday – Friday | 3:00 PM – 10:00 PM | $19/hour + bonuses<br><br>Inbound Customer Service Representative Required Qualification:<br><br>- Friendly, outgoing personality with a customer-first mindset<br>- Excellent verbal communication and active listening skills<br>- Dependable and committed to consistent attendance<br>- Ability to follow structured processes and meet performance targets<br>- Receptive to feedback and quick to apply coaching<br>- Previous experience in customer service, hospitality, sales, or leadership is a plus<br>- Must be at least 18 years old<br><br>Inbound Customer Service Representative Key Responsibilities:<br><br>- Take incoming calls from guests ready to plan and book their vacations<br>- Assist with choosing destinations, selecting travel dates, and completing reservations<br>- Collect payments and ensure booking details are accurate and complete<br>- Answer questions, resolve concerns, and offer helpful travel suggestions<br>- Build product and destination knowledge to deliver confident, informed service<br>- Use strong communication to highlight value, address hesitations, and create urgency<br>- Bring positive energy to each interaction and exceed service expectations<br>- Embrace coaching and continuous improvement to support personal and team growth<br>- Hit performance goals and contribute to a high-achieving team environment<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Inbound Customer Service Representative - 4 Day Work Week]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32480498]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/inbound-customer-service-representative-4-day-work-week-32480498/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[SC]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract to Hire]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$17/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Myrtle Beach, SC · Onsite<br><br>Employment Type: Contract to Hire<br><br>Pay Rate: $17/hour<br><br>We&#x27;re hiring upbeat, motivated individuals for our Inbound Customer Service team. This isn&#x27;t your typical 9–5. With a 4-day workweek (Saturday – Tuesday), you&#x27;ll enjoy longer time off while helping guests make the most of their vacation packages. You&#x27;ll guide callers through planning and booking their trips, offering expert advice, resolving concerns, and creating a positive, memorable experience from start to finish. If you&#x27;re energized by great conversations and love the idea of a compressed schedule (Saturday – Tuesday), this is the perfect opportunity.<br><br>What we&#x27;re looking for:<br><br>- A friendly, outgoing personality with a customer-first mindset<br>- Strong verbal communication and active listening skills<br>- Dependable attendance—especially on your 4 dedicated workdays (Saturday – Tuesday)<br>- Ability to follow structured processes and meet performance targets<br>- Openness to feedback and coaching<br>- Experience in customer service, hospitality, sales, or leadership is a plus<br><br>What you&#x27;ll do during your 4-day workweek:<br><br>- Answer inbound calls from guests ready to book their vacations<br>- Help choose destinations, travel dates, and finalize reservations<br>- Process payments and ensure booking details are accurate<br>- Answer questions, resolve concerns, and offer helpful travel suggestions<br>- Use product and destination knowledge to deliver confident, informed service<br>- Communicate clearly to highlight value, build urgency, and address objections<br>- Exceed service expectations with a positive, professional tone<br>- Embrace coaching and growth to keep improving<br>- Meet individual and team performance goals within your 4-day shift window<br><br>Schedule &amp; pay:<br><br>- Sat–Tues, 9:00 AM – 6:00 PM<br>- Pay: $17/hour + performance bonuses<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Outbound Call Center Representative]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32480494]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/outbound-call-center-representative-32480494/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[SC]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract to Hire]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$17-$19/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Job Title: Outbound Call Center Representative<br><br>Location: Myrtle Beach, SC – Onsite<br><br>Shifts:<br><br>- AM Shift: Mon–Fri, 9:00 AM – 4:00 PM<br>- PM Shift: Mon–Fri, 3:00 PM – 10:00 PM<br><br>Pay Rate:<br><br>- AM Shift: $17/HR + performance bonuses<br>- PM Shift: $19/hour + performance bonuses<br><br>We&#x27;re hiring Outbound Call Center Representatives to join our team in Myrtle Beach, SC. In this role, you&#x27;ll engage with guests by phone to help them plan and book their ideal vacation experience. If you&#x27;re confident, personable, and motivated by helping people create unforgettable getaways, this is an excellent opportunity to grow your career in a fun, fast-paced environment.<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Energetic, outgoing personality with a strong customer service mindset<br>- Excellent verbal communication and active listening skills<br>- Reliable, punctual, and committed to strong attendance<br>- Comfortable working in a structured, goal-driven environment<br>- Open to feedback and eager to learn and improve<br>- Previous experience in customer service, hospitality, or sales is a plus<br>- Must be 18 years of age or older<br><br>Day-to-Day Responsibilities<br><br>- Place outbound calls to guests interested in planning vacations<br>- Guide customers through destination options, booking dates, and reservation details<br>- Process payments and accurately confirm all booking information<br>- Provide helpful recommendations and address guest questions or concerns<br>- Build strong product and destination knowledge to better assist guests<br>- Use effective sales techniques to create urgency and drive bookings<br>- Deliver friendly, engaging service on every call<br>- Participate in coaching and development sessions to enhance performance<br>- Meet or exceed daily and weekly performance goals<br><br>Company Benefits &amp; Culture<br><br>- Weekly pay with performance-based bonuses<br>- Health, dental, and vision insurance<br>- 401(k) with employer match<br>- Paid training and vacation travel credits<br>- PTO awarded after tenure milestones<br>- Casual, team-oriented office environment<br>- Plus additional perks designed to reward your hard work<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Manager]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32415447]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/engineering-manager-32415447/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$112,800-$143,100/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Hybrid in York, Pennsylvania<br><br>Pay Rate: $112,000 – $143,000 / year<br><br>Employment Type: Full-Time, Direct Hire<br><br>Introduction<br><br>Our client is seeking an Engineering Manager to lead multidisciplinary engineering teams responsible for automation and balance of plant products and systems used in hydroelectric power generation.<br><br>This senior leadership position will oversee engineering activities throughout the complete project lifecycle, including proposal development, detailed design, manufacturing, construction, commissioning, and operational support. The Engineering Manager will be accountable for engineering safety, quality, technical performance, project schedules, budgets, reliability, and the successful delivery of customer solutions.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Lead and manage multiple engineering teams and disciplines, including automation, balance of plant electrical, and balance of plant mechanical engineering.<br>- Provide supervision, mentorship, training, and technical guidance to engineering leaders, engineers, and department team members.<br>- Develop detailed engineering plans, schedules, resource requirements, and labor-hour estimates during the Offer-to-Order phase.<br>- Ensure engineering plans are successfully implemented throughout the Order-to-Cash phase.<br>- Oversee the development of safe, reliable, timely, and cost-effective engineering deliverables.<br>- Ensure the effective and timely completion of contract designs, layouts, calculations, procedures, manuals, and technical documentation.<br>- Coordinate engineering support for the commissioning, field testing, operation, and maintenance of hydroelectric projects.<br>- Ensure departmental and integrated engineering standards are consistently followed.<br>- Lead key engineering processes, including design strategies, design reviews, design freezes, lessons learned, and technical risk assessments.<br>- Serve as a key technical representative for the organization when communicating complex engineering matters internally and externally.<br>- Coordinate integrated engineering teams to optimize modernization and new equipment designs.<br>- Support projects involving efficiency improvements, power output uprates, equipment life extensions, and safe and reliable plant operations.<br>- Support annual financial goals and long-term engineering and business objectives.<br>- Promote engineering development through Root Cause Analysis reports, Corrective Actions, and updates to the Lessons Learned database.<br>- Provide engineering support to proposal teams, sourcing, manufacturing, field operations, and other departments throughout the product lifecycle.<br>- Evaluate technical risks during both the proposal and project execution phases.<br>- Conduct and participate in design reviews, Failure Modes and Effects Analysis processes, and other engineering risk assessments.<br>- Maintain and improve engineering standards, technical design guidelines, manuals, and procedures.<br>- Ensure engineering activities are completed on schedule, within budget, and according to contractual and technical requirements.<br>- Drive a culture of engineering excellence, accountability, collaboration, and continuous improvement.<br><br>Requirements<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in engineering.<br>- At least 15 years of relevant engineering experience within automation and/or balance of plant environments.<br>- Experience within energy, hydroelectric power generation, or a closely related power generation environment.<br>- At least 10 years of experience as an engineering lead, supervisor, or manager.<br>- Proven experience successfully leading multidisciplinary engineering teams and complex engineering projects.<br>- Experience managing engineering activities throughout proposal, design, manufacturing, construction, commissioning, and operational support phases.<br>- Experience developing engineering project plans, schedules, resource estimates, and labor-hour estimates.<br>- Strong understanding of automation and balance of plant products, systems, and engineering deliverables.<br>- Experience evaluating technical risks through design reviews, FMEA processes, Root Cause Analysis, and Corrective Actions.<br>- Demonstrated ability to deliver engineering projects on schedule and within budget.<br>- Strong leadership, teamwork, collaboration, and mentoring abilities.<br>- Excellent verbal and written communication skills.<br>- Strong organizational, prioritization, and time management skills.<br>- Meticulous attention to detail and accuracy.<br>- Ability to proactively plan upcoming work based on project and business needs.<br>- Ability to thrive in a fast-paced engineering and project environment.<br>- Ability to drive a culture focused on engineering quality, safety, reliability, and continuous improvement.<br>- Ability to travel as required.<br>- Ability to work within office, field, manufacturing, and industrial environments.<br>- Ability to occasionally lift up to 50 pounds and climb ladders when required.<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Advanced degree in engineering or a related technical discipline.<br>- Experience leading engineering teams within a global power generation or hydroelectric organization.<br>- Experience supporting modernization, equipment uprate, life-extension, and new hydroelectric power generation projects.<br>- Experience coordinating engineering activities across global business units, manufacturing facilities, suppliers, field teams, and corporate engineering groups.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sourcing Manager]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32496368]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/sourcing-manager-32496368/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[PA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Starting at $112,000/year]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: York, PA (Onsite)<br>Employment Type: Direct Hire<br>Pay Rate: Up to $112,000<br><br>Our client is a global leader in industrial technology with deep roots in hydro, energy, and power systems. They are bringing on a Sourcing Manager to lead supply chain activities across complex, custom-engineered projects. This is a full-time, direct hire role based in York, PA, reporting into the Director of Strategic Sourcing.<br><br>Responsibilities<br><br>- Lead and manage all supply chain activities for assigned projects from offer to order through order to completion<br>- Develop and execute project-specific sourcing strategies focused on cost, risk, and schedule<br>- Perform market analysis and negotiate with suppliers on both technical and commercial terms<br>- Review customer specifications and provide procurement-related input as needed<br>- Coordinate purchasing activities with global Material Group leadership<br>- Track, forecast, and report on project purchasing budgets during review meetings<br>- Execute purchases of materials and services in compliance with established policies<br>- Build and maintain collaborative relationships with suppliers to drive quality improvement and cost reduction<br>- Support internal customers on key project requirements<br>- Contribute to special projects as assigned by leadership<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Experience in sourcing, supply chain, procurement, or project management within a relevant industry; the client will consider candidates ranging from junior/entry-level up to 5-8 years of experience depending on background and fit<br>- Background in EPC, construction, mining, aerospace, marine, government/DOD, gas, renewable energy, or low-volume manufacturing<br>- Strong negotiation skills with the ability to work cross-functionally across global teams<br>- Proficiency in SAP ERP<br>- Excellent written and verbal communication skills in English<br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in Supply Chain Management, Engineering, or a related field (preferred but not required)<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Previous experience managing or developing a sourcing team<br>- Hydro power or power systems industry experience<br>- Familiarity with Power BI<br>- Ability to read and interpret engineering drawings and specifications<br>- Knowledge of FAR/government purchasing compliance<br><br>Company Benefits and Culture<br><br>The client offers a collaborative, cross-functional environment with a global footprint and strong technical culture. This role carries direct impact on project outcomes and offers meaningful exposure across supply chain, engineering, and project management functions. Compensation and benefits details will be provided during the interview process.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Purchasing]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32538036]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/director-of-purchasing-32538036/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Oshkosh]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[WI]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Placement]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[Competitive Salary]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Appleton, WI (on-site)<br><br>Salary: $160,000 + bonus<br><br>Introduction<br>Our client, a global leader in the pulp and paper industry, is seeking a Director of Purchasing to lead strategic and operational procurement execution across North America. This role owns cost savings, on-time delivery, supplier quality, and productivity KPIs while serving as a member of the North American leadership team.<br><br>Required Qualifications<br><br>- Proven procurement experience, including a leadership role<br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree with a technical or business major<br>- Strong coaching, developing, mentoring, and leadership skills<br>- Strategic mindset with ability to develop and execute differentiated plans that deliver financial results<br>- Strong customer centricity and communication skills<br>- Action-oriented with strong attention to detail<br>- Familiarity with MRP/ERP systems and data analytics tools, including SAP and Power BI<br>- Ability to run queries and compile data for data-driven decisions<br><br>Preferred Qualifications<br><br>- Pulp and paper industry experience<br><br>Day-to-Day Responsibilities<br><br>- Develop and implement a regional procurement strategy aligned with overall group strategy for cost-effective, timely, high-quality sourcing<br>- Oversee the NA procurement team, ensuring focus on safety, cost competitiveness, OTD, supplier quality, and productivity KPIs<br>- Lead and manage tough purchasing negotiations, including frame agreements, major purchase order releases, and quality/back-charge negotiations<br>- Implement an effective regional Supply Chain Management program in partnership with the NA Logistics/GBS group<br>- Drive alignment of procurement activities within NA and across divisions for consistent sourcing strategies<br>- Lead and mentor procurement team members to improve individual and team performance<br>- Promote a culture of ownership, teamwork, respect, and customer centricity; drive continuous improvement<br>- Ensure compliance with People &amp; Culture policies and support an engaging work environment<br>- Partner with sales, applications, operations, product, and project management to align on customer needs<br>- Lead major transformation initiatives, including automation, digitalization, and process redesign<br>- Champion safety in all activities<br>- Stand, walk, and sit frequently throughout the day; occasionally reach, lift, stoop, or crouch<br>- Occasional domestic and international travel required<br><br>Company Benefits and Culture<br>Our client operates as part of a global organization with a strong emphasis on ownership, teamwork, respect, and customer centricity. The company invests in leadership development and continuous improvement, and this role sits on the North American leadership team with direct visibility into strategic decision-making.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Clinical Proofreader/Editor]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32535692]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/clinical-proofreader-editor-32535692/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[New York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[NY]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Fully remote]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$25–$28/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Clinical Writer/Editor Role Overview:<br>4 Corner Resources is currently seeking a detail-oriented Clinical Proofreader/Editor to ensure compliance, accuracy, and quality in member and provider correspondence. This position involves reviewing clinical system events, collaborating with internal teams, and ensuring adherence to state and federal regulations while maintaining corporate branding standards.<br><br>This position is a 100% remote role. It is a 6-month contract with the potential for extension.<br><br>Clinical Writer/Editor Key Responsibilities:<br><br>- Complete assigned correspondence tasks promptly and within designated timeframes.<br>- Identify gaps in processes and provide actionable feedback to reduce errors and improve overall quality.<br>- Review member and provider communications to ensure consistency with the clinical system (TruCare) and compliance with regulatory guidelines.<br>- Audit and analyze correspondence to confirm accuracy with TruCare records and ensure the appropriate templates are utilized correctly.<br>- Work closely with care managers, leadership, and peer reviewers to maintain compliance with regulatory-mandated communications.<br>- Assess correspondence for accurate medical terminology and adherence to departmental policies and applicable regulations.<br>- Support the organization in managing the lifecycle of correspondence, including creation, storage, secure retrieval, and proper archiving.<br>- Maintain consistency in all correspondence by adhering to corporate branding standards.<br>- Take on other responsibilities as assigned.<br><br>Clinical Writer/Editor Qualifications:<br><br>- Possession of a high school diploma or equivalent (GED).<br>- Exceptional skills in both written and verbal communication.<br>- Strong abilities in organization and time management.<br>- Ability to meet production targets of 35 letters per day and 200 letters per week.<br>- Proven critical thinking and creative problem-solving capabilities.<br>- Relevant professional experience within the healthcare industry.<br>- An associate degree in a healthcare-related field is preferred.<br>- Working knowledge of MS SharePoint.<br>- Hands-on experience with Utilization Management, government healthcare programs, and managed care processes, including organizational determinations, approvals, denials, appeals, and grievances.<br>- Adept at performing moderately complex communication tasks, with experience in training others and collaborating across teams.<br>- Demonstrated adaptability to evolving tasks and a professional, objective approach to collaboration.<br><br>Clinical Writer/Editor Pay Rate:<br><br>- Starting at $25+/HR<br><br>Clinical Writer/Editor Schedule:<br><br>- Regular Hours: Monday–Friday, 11:00 AM to 8:00 PM (ET)<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 09 Jul 2026 00:00:00 EST]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[32544142]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.4cornerresources.com/jobs/software-qa-engineer-32544142/]]></url>
    <company><![CDATA[4 Corner Resources]]></company>
    <city><![CDATA[Orlando]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[FL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract to Hire]]></jobtype>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[]]></remotetype>
    <salary><![CDATA[$43-$55/hour]]></salary>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Must be local to Orlando, FL.<br><br>4 Corner Resources is seeking a Software QA Engineer to join one of our clients in a hybrid work environment. This role is ideal for a quality focused engineer with strong automation experience who enjoys building scalable test solutions, validating APIs, and integrating testing into modern CI/CD pipelines. The ideal candidate has experience working in Agile environments, collaborating closely with developers, and ensuring software quality across complex applications and system integrations.<br><br>Responsibilities:<br><br>- Design, develop, and maintain scalable automated test scripts for web applications, APIs, and mobile applications.<br>- Build and execute functional, regression, performance, and load testing using BlazeMeter.<br>- Validate complex data flows, system integrations, and operational platforms across multiple projects.<br>- Test REST APIs and backend services to ensure functionality, reliability, and performance.<br>- Deploy, configure, and maintain automated testing environments within Microsoft Azure.<br>- Integrate automated functional and performance testing into Azure DevOps Pipelines for continuous integration and continuous delivery.<br>- Investigate, isolate, and troubleshoot software defects while partnering closely with developers to identify root causes and resolve issues.<br>- Improve testing processes, automation coverage, and defect quality to reduce rework and increase release confidence.<br>- Collaborate with cross functional teams to remove blockers and support successful software delivery.<br><br>Qualifications:<br><br>- Bachelor&#x27;s degree in Computer Science, Information Technology, Engineering, or a related field, or equivalent practical experience.<br>- 3+ years of experience as an SDET or QA Automation Engineer in an Agile environment.<br>- Strong programming experience in Python, Java, JavaScript, or C#.<br>- Experience building automated test frameworks using Selenium, Playwright, Appium, or similar tools.<br>- Experience testing REST APIs using Postman, SoapUI, Swagger, or code based automation.<br>- Experience with Azure DevOps Pipelines and CI/CD automation.<br>- Practical experience working within Microsoft Azure cloud environments.<br>- Experience with Jira and SQL required. MongoDB experience is a plus.<br>- Strong understanding of regression testing, API validation, defect management, and software quality best practices.<br><br>Preferred Qualifications:<br><br>- Hands on experience with BlazeMeter for functional, performance, and load testing.<br>- Experience writing Azure DevOps YAML pipelines.<br>- Experience with Docker or Kubernetes.<br>- Experience writing intermediate to advanced SQL queries for database validation.<br><br>Additional Details:<br><br>- Hybrid schedule in Orlando, FL, three days per week onsite.<br>- Pay starting at $43 per hour.<br>- Contract to hire opportunity based on performance, workload, and business needs.<br><br>Apply through this board and our recruiting team will be in touch.</p>]]></description>
  </job>
</source>